<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
  <title>Tom Probyn's personal website</title>
  <link>https://tomprobyn.uk</link>
  <description>Tom Probyn's personal website, for anything I find marginally interesting and worth sharing.</description>
  <item>
    <title>Complete website rebuild!</title>
    <link>https://tomprobyn.uk</link>
    <description>Since getting an entirely new URL for the site, I decided to entirely re-build and restructure it. Now, everything is built on Markdown and compiled to HTML using a Python Script, and the process of writing is significantly smoother than it was before (having to wrangle with HTML manually). There aren't too many user-facing changes (apart from the new structure and URL) so you should still feel comfortable navigating, but do stop by the entirely new home page and have a good old poke around!</description>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>Problem solving and the transmitter map</title>
    <link>https://tomprobyn.uk/blogs/ideas/data_wrangling_relays.html</link>
    <description>In which I slowly loose the pithy little that remains of my sanity trying to find an excel document published as a PDF from 2007, and shoehorn the data into Google Earth. About as nail-biting as it gets round here!</description>
  </item>
  <item>
  <title>The new site is complete(ish)</title>
    <link>https://tomprobyn.uk/blogs/ideas/new_site_links.html</link>
    <description>Please look out for any broken links and send an E-Mail if you find one!</description>
  </item>
    <item>
  <title>Great floods in the Water of Leith</title>
    <link>https://tomprobyn.uk/blogs/walks/floods_water_leith.html</link>
    <description>An exceptional walk through somewhere with which I am already incredibly familiar, but in a circumstance wholly distinguishable from the usual</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Life in the slow line</title>
    <link>https://tomprobyn.uk/blogs/ideas/the_slow_line.html</link>
    <description>Deliberately slowing down the internet to end our reliance on it</description>
  </item>
    <item>
    <title>Web index updates</title>
    <link>https://tomprobyn.uk/blogs/projects/web_index.html</link>
    <description>I should probably create a project-specific RSS feed for the web index, but I have changed some things there and added links.</description>
  </item>
    <item>
    <title>Magnificent birds in Northern Scotland</title>
    <link>https://tomprobyn.uk/blogs/walks/northern_scotland_birds.html</link>
    <description>A short entry on some interesting bird sightings on a recent trip to Northern Scotland</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The ambiguous world of perfect pitch</title>
    <link>https://tomprobyn.uk/blogs/ideas/perfect_pitch.html</link>
    <description>An extensive guide to knowing how your brain processes musical pitch for people who were never musically trained</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>!!GROW_UP!! is out now!</title>
    <link>https://youtu.be/CIdlXb3Y030</link>
    <description>!!GROW_UP!! is a song which I've been working on for a very long while. It's hard to describe quite what it is, but I feel Hyperpop is the closest I can come to it  - but it certainly isn't hyperpop either!</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The simplified ratio clock</title>
    <link>https://tomprobyn.uk/blogs/projects/ratio_clock/ratio_clock.html</link>
    <description>A very stupid and utterly useless idea I had and made because the alternative was not making it. WARNING: Contains maths!</description>
  </item>
   <item>
    <title>Notes</title>
    <link>https://tomprobyn.uk/notes</link>
    <description>I've started a new section of the website containing notes, which are less organised than blogs. Notes has its own RSS feed, which you can find on the Feed page</description>
  </item>
</channel>

</rss> 